Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 15
When that person sometimes goes to meet her old man from before then comes back home and smiles at me,
emotions of anger, despair, and sadness take turns in overcoming me.
I'd like to ask that person why she does that,
but this foolish man is too scared to open his mouth that can't even say a word.
Leave!
The things you couldn't object to, Dad,
I wanted to try.
How she could do such a thing. Taking advantage of someone...
And how she could do that to a person like you.
How she could try to fool you.
I could've told her to leave immediately.
But... I didn't do that, Dad.
I don't want to kick her out so simply.
I didn't want to resolve it so simply,
♫ ♫I am living day after day
so I held back.
♫ In your name when tears appear, ♫I
♫  can't bear it ♫I
What I'm going to do...
So I can't laugh
Wait and see, Dad.
You were going to tell Unni?
You're going tell Unni that I've found out?
You don't need to.
Mom.
If Unni finds out, I'm sure it'll be noisy. I don't want it to be noisy at all.
Let's just keep quiet and let this pass.
Don't think of anything else.
Mom you just quietly live as the madam of Woon Hak Pavilion and as my mom.
You're going to live this way.
Because of the problems with the contract, I'm sure Unni will constantly on the phone at the winery.
Pack Unni a lunch box, Mom. I'll take it to her so that she can eat.
I know you don't make the decisions,
so please let me meet the person who does.
Please do this for me.
Sorry for coming out of the blue and asking for such a difficult favor
after not having contacted you since we were classmates.
But, I'll be sure to make it up to you.
I won't ever forget your kindness. Please, do this for me.
We do need the freeze dry producing equipment from your company.
And of course we'll naturally cover all the expenses.
I already sent these to you via email, but these are all the documents.
If you get a chance, please read them.
Hello? My name is Hong Gi Hoon, the one who called you before. I'm on my way there now-
Anyway, you will meet me because I'm not going to give up.
I'll see you in 10 minutes.
So, he's from HongJoo Winery?
Yes. He said he wanted to meet you.
It seemed like he was really interested in your yeast.
Right. Is there any relative named Jang Taek Geun in your family?
Mom won't tell me.
There is none. I already told you there wasn't.
Is that so? I got it.
What are you saying you got?
Yes. You said there's no one.
I'm just saying I got that.
Let's go to Hong Joo Winery. To the person you met with before.
I have to hear directly exactly what his intentions are.
Go alone. I need to stay with Mom.
It seems that Mom is longing for Dad lately.
I need to stay with Mom.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Then, would you like to stay with Mom?
I'll be the one going around for the cooperative work.
This food... Please eat it before you go.
Don't starve and stumble.
How can you get skinnier day by day?
That's why you keep collapsing so often.
Is there any relative named Jang Taek Geun in your family?
My Daughter
We have to make sure that Ahjussi Jang doesn't show up again, Jeong Woo.
Don't worry, he's not going to show up.
He definitely can't show up again.
I also asked him that.
That if he's starving, to contact me without telling anything to you.
He said he'd do that, so don't worry.
Have you been eating? You didn't, right?
It's delicious! Why did you make the kimbap, Mom?
Joon Soo wants to eat gimbap, so I'm going to feed him some when he comes back from his kindergarten.
Ah, I see.
Leave that to Grandmother and Ahjumma. Let's go together to pick Joon Soo up, Mom.
Let's wait in front of his kindergarten and bring him home.
Why should we? The bus will bring him anyway.
Grandmother from Yeon Cheon
Yes, Grandmother.I wanted to call you but I completely forgot.
Yes. Mom?
What about Mom?
I don't know what you're going to tell me, but please don't do it, Grandmother.
I'll go and see you soon, so please don't tell me now.
Yes. I'll hang up now. Yes, Grandmother, take care.
Mom, hurry up.
Why is he taking so long?
Isn't it past the time he's supposed to come out? Right, Mom?
Can't you tell me in advance how far you'll go?
I don't know how far I'll go either. I'm sorry.
Are you planning to go to the end?
I am planning to go to the end.
Alright then. It's not as though I don't have other ways either.
What are you talking about? I'm not sure what you're talking about, but leave now.
I'm expecting to receive a visitor and it's about time for her to arrive.
Is it okay for you to run into them?
What time did you say the meeting was with Dae Seong True Winemakers' Goo Eun Jo?
I'll be nearby so call me when you're done, Noona.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I don't want to tell anyone about you yet.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
An outstanding corporation such as Dae Seong True Winemakers is attempting to stand up utilizing Japanese corporate funds.
I find that regretful so I spoke.
Our company is probably much better than Japan, on a patriotic level.
Is that why you interfered with our contract?
Because it's more patriotic to accept Hong Joo Ga's investment rather than from a Japanese company?
I'll get straight to the point.
We'll support you so that you can only continue doing research on the yeast.
I also won't touch Dae Seong True Winemaker's name.
I sincerely think it's unfortunate
that someone as incredible as Goo Dae Sung passed away.
His name remaining in the company and products names...
I believe that has meaning.
So, in short it means that you want us to hand over Dae Seong True Winemakers.
I'm not asking you to give it up for free.
Thank you.
You're thanking me?
I hadn't known that Dae Seong True Winemakers had such a threatening potential.
I'd been working hard because I have to build it up no matter what,
but thank you for helping me realize that Dae Sung True Winemakers is large enough
to make the country's largest rice winery, Hong Joo Ga, want to acquire it.
It's also good to know that the conscience of such a large corporation only amounts to this much.
Thank you. You've given me strength to get it back on its feet somehow.
I'll just pretend I didn't hear your offer to provide support for my research on the yeast.
You're saying this even though I told you the amount of money?
I'm saying it's even more impossible because you told me the amount you'd pay.
If you're willing to offer me that much money for the yeast that I've discovered,
that means the market value of my yeast is worth multiples of that amount.
Thank you for that too. That's become a large source of strength as well.
If things go well, I'll repay you by buying you a meal.
Also, I won't forget it.
I won't forget a single thing you've done to us.
I'll repay you for that too, so wait and be prepared.
Mom, let's take a family photo.
Mom, Eun Jo, Joon Soo and me...
We don't have a family photo.
We should've taken one when Dad was still here.
But Dad was quite busy, I guess.
Let's take one and hang it up.
In your room, my room, and Unni's room.
We should also print one for each family member to put in our wallets.
Joon Soo!
Joon Soo, no. Hurry and come down. Don't do that. It's dangerous.
- No!
- Quick, come to Noona.
A little girl like her actually dares to challenge
the Song Kang Sook who has even beat God and the Buddha.
A little puppy, who isn't even a day old, is showing her teeth
at someone who has never even feared God or the Buddha.
Let's play!
That newborn puppy...is even scarier than a ghost.
- Hyo Seon is here!
- Joon Soo is here!
Mom!
Mom isn't here.
Not here?
- Joon Soo.
- Yeah?
Go ask Grandma for food and eat.
Okay.
You're leaving? How can you leave like this?
How can you leave after the child grew feelings for you?
This damn destiny, damn Song Kang Sook.
Now I realize the worst part of my fate is this family.
God, Buddha, thank you for at least making me realize now.
You've finally come to your senses.
Stay right there!
Why am I seeing that scary woman?
Why am I seeing that evil b*tch?
Where are you going? You can't go! Who said you can go?
Don't stop, Ajusshi.
- Let me go!
- Where are you going?!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Give me my bag!
Let go! Let go, you b*tch. You evil b*tch.
You demon! You're the worst in this world!
You demon! Get your hands off me!
Where are you going? You can't go.
You have to live under my torture until the day you die, Mom.
If I wanted to watch you run away, I would've kicked you out already.
You think I wouldn't do anything?
Why don't you just swear at me instead?! Call me a b*tch, call me a wh*re.
Why do you have to call me Mom with that faint smile on your face?
You're a hundred times scarier than I am, you know that?
Watch your mouth, Mom. Someone might hear you.
A wh*re?
What?
That is something out of this world,
just for you, God and me to know.
Even God doesn't want anyone else to know, so keep your mouth shut!
How can you say such words?
Where did you learn to be so rude?
How can you do this to your father?
How can you do that with a human masK? It's better to curse at me, you bitch.
If there were not Joon Soo between you and me,
I would also have done that.
My little brother, Joon Soo...
My father's son, Joon Soo...
How could I insult my father's son?
Should I try it? Should I spit in Joon Soo's face
and call his mother a wh*re?
Say it! Why can't you?!
How can I spit in my father son's face?!
Oh no...
Don't touch!
Don't try to apologize. I won't believe you.
Are you trying to ask me for forgiveness, Mom?
The person who should forgive you is already dead! Why are you begging me?
Just live like this forever.
Live as a sinner.
Do you think I'll forgive you?
Do you think I'll let you live with ease?
Get on my back.
Get on my back, you awful brat.
Call ended
Your call cannot be connected. After the beep, you will be connected to voic--.
Where in the world are you and what are you doing?
With a whole mountain of work, you neglected it and are putting on antics like this.
I want to let you know. I truly will not leave you alone.
Jeong Woo. Jeong Woo!
For now, we're going to make the wine.
We're going to make the wine and give some to the village associations, funerals, and feasts.
I'm going to do that so people don't forget our wine.
Get ready.
But, where are you going now?
To the research lab. Let go of me.
It's late, go tomorrow. Do you know what time it is?
Stop fooling around and finish up what you were doing so you can get off work.
Go in, I have something to say to you.
- What kind of person are you?
- I said let's go in.
You plan on behaving as such and have thoughts of receiving wages from someone else's company?
What kind of person are you? What are you thinking?!
I don't need a worker like you. Resign immediately.
We... can make wine, Eun Jo.
The freeze dried line that the Japanese had cancelled
was identical to probiotics made by pharmaceutical companies.
I went to around ten of those places, and one place returned the call.
You got a call?
Their conditions are demanding though.
First, the expenses will be high for a while.
I will carefully consider the costs and benefits from this point forward.
If the value is worth enough for us to bear the expense.
I'll search for a way that doesn't harm Dae Seong True Winemakers.
If the expenses are still too much, I'm going to meet them again and try to negotiate the price further.
What's second?
The second is that they found out the possibility of using the yeast you discovered as a medical raw material.
It won't be right away but after some time
you'll have to cooperate with them on the research.
Of course, this is top secret.
Is there a third condition?
After the summer break, I have to work for their company.
What?
The person in-charge of the pharmaceutical company I met with
is my seonbae, who attended the same school, when I studied in America.
She said she needs me.
I said I would do it.
If I'm going to go, we need to stand Dae Seong True Winemakers on its feet now.
We need to raise it up firmly so that it wouldn't tremble
even if someone tries touching it or shaking it up.
You ...
said you'd do it?
Yeah.
So, you're leaving here?
So,
you've promised to leave Dae Seong True Winemakers.
Yeah. That's right.
I promise I'll devote my life to work until I leave.
Believe me.
It's been more than an hour. How long are you going to be like this?
Starting from a long time ago,
I didn't look forward to anything when I opened my eyes every morning.
I would either wake up in some man's house
or some hotel room. It was always either one of the two.
The words I heard most often were tirades from Mom in the morning.
To the tirading mom, the curses those men pour out onto her.
The sounds of the shattering of household goods.
It was like that.
Starting from one day,
I didn't hear those sounds anymore.
I thought that it would just be temporary,
and that I'd hear what I didn't want to hear again.
I didn't believe it, since it was a peace that would be broken soon.
Because if I believed it and was betrayed, I'd be the one in pain.
But still, no matter how many days passed,
I couldn't hear my mom cursing. It seemed too good to be true.
And then...
Opening my eyes in the morning was becoming fun.
I wanted to sleep early at night.
Because once I slept and woke up, it'd be morning.
Since I need to sleep and wake up in the morning
for another day with him to begin.
Every time I turned my face, there was someone who made me happy just be being there.
How dare I... I didn't even expect much.
No matter where I went,
if that person were there, that was enough for me.
Because even if I didn't see him for a little while,
When I saw him again, I felt the joy I may have felt from not having seen someone in 100 million years.
Award
That was enough for me.
Whenever you hold that in your hand, think of me.
Was that too much to ask for?
When just seeing him was enough for me...
He left.
♫  In your name when tears appear,  ♫
But...
He said he's leaving again.
♫  So I can't laugh  ♫
He said he'd leave again.
Living feels like hell.
Should I stop him from going?
Should I snap his legs?
Can you do that for me?
If you can, can you try?
Don't cry.
It's for the best.
If he leaves this time,
he probably won't come back.
If he doesn't come back,
he won't leave again either.
It's for the best.
It really is, Jeong Woo.
Dae Seong True Winemakers Takju Development Budgeting
Can't you tell me in advance how far you'll go?
I don't know how far I'll go either. I'm sorry.
Are you going to go all the way?
I'm going all the way.
No! I said no!
Stay still!
Where are you touching? Don't touch me.
You said you don't want to go to the hospital. You should at least put some ointment on.
Will you be able to walk like this?
Even if I can't walk, it's my problem! It's none of your business.
What is this?
I asked what is this?
I hurt my soles, so I need to apply some ointment.
Mom keeps hurting me.
How did you get hurt?
Apply it gently, Mom. It hurts.
Lift your foot up.
Have a good meal.
It's beef leg bone broth. I've been craving it.
Pick up your spoon, Mom.
What are you doing?
I'm putting salt in.
What?
You can't taste anything, so you keep putting salt in?
It's not salty at all.
Did you catch a cold or something?
If you're really sick, you can't taste anything.
No.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
You...
I said I'm fine! Why are you being like this?
Stop talking and lie down.
I said I'm fine!
Mom!
Your temperature is over 40 degrees! It's strange that you don't feel anything.
Let's try to get your fever down first. I'll go get the oriental medicine Grandfather from the clinic.
Mom, there's something really wrong with her. Get the grandfather to take a look at her,
and if he says there's something wrong, we'll go to the hospital.
Okay. Hurry and go to work.
I'm taking care of things at work. Don't worry.
- Really?
- Yes.
Things are going well. I think the pharmaceutical company can lend us their freeze-dry production line.
- Really?
- Yes.
Hurry and go. Don't trouble her with work.
Rest up.
You still have the energy to fight with me when you have such a high fever?
Yes. I'm full of energy.
Close your eyes and sleep.
No!
Go away.
I've never seen someone like you.
I've committed so many sins, so maybe meeting someone like you
is fate... fate that brought us together.
Everything before wasn't punishment. This is my real punishment.
This isn't even the beginning yet.
There is a special person.
A special person?
Then, how special am I to you?
It's so nice here! This is where rice wine is stored.
I might get drunk here.
- This tastes so good.
- It does, right?
If I get drunk because of this, you have to take care of me, okay?
- What's going on in there?
- I don't know either.
Dae Seong True Winemaker
I've listed out the expenses. I've also marked what needs to be reduced.
In my opinion, the best choice is to use this production line.
It's best to hurry and make a decision.
My sunbae from the pharmaceutical company just left.
She said she wanted to come take a look, so I told her to come. Things look positive.
Is it the sunbae that scouted you?
Yeah, that sunbae.
She laughs a lot.
Yeah, she's someone who always makes people laugh.
She's a happy person.
You were laughing a lot with her too.
Yeah,
she makes all the people around her laugh.
Let me know what else we need until we make a decision.
- Okay.
- Are you going to the research lab?
Yeah.
Should I take you there?
You must be relieved.
- What?
- About getting a better job.
After all, you're someone who should've been working in marketing at a huge company from the start.
You just didn't have any excuse to leave me and Hyo Seon after Hyo Seon's father passed.
Right? You must think you've finally found a blessing in this mess.
Congratulations. It's great for you.
Yeah. Thank you.
Who was the girl messing around with you by the lake yesterday?
- Good work, everyone.
- Good work.
Hi, Sunbae.
Yes.
Really? Yeah. Are you sure?
Yes. I got it. Thank you, Sunbae.
You can't run away. You can't run away!
You can't run away. You can't run away.
You're really punishing me cruelly.
You two are really crueler than I am.
Dae Seong True Cooperative's production line has started.
The freeze dried yeast from Nihon pharmaceutical
has arrived at Dae Seong True Winemaker's factory.
They've started production?
Yes.
They have a buyer?
- You said there is?
- Yes.
Who is it?
Gi Hoon successfully persuaded Miura-san.
They already received a dumping price for Hong Joo Ga's wine,
so it wouldn't hurt them much if it doesn't sell.
What did you say? Are you serious now?
- The taste...
- The taste?
- They found that the taste of Dae Seong True Winemakers' takju
is much better than Hongjoo Family's in market research in Japan.
Other alcohol distribution companies seem to be showing interest in them as well.
It's also because our wine has been going around for almost free due to us dumping,
so they had a lot of chances to compare our wine with Dae Seong True Winemakers is another reason.
It seems product dumping was a big mistake.
Do you have anything else to say?
You're reporting this so shamelessly?
Do you have anything else to report, Head Manager Park?
Yes, I do.
Resignation Letter
I believe you'll accept this. I'll see myself off.
Only that one? Go quickly and come back to take more boxes.
Put it on straight like that, stretched and flat like so
Hello, Dong Soo? Wait a moment.
Yes. What are you saying?
I found out a few things, but I had to confirm some things first.
About the export scam in Japan, apparently it was Hong Joo Ga...
Hong Joo Ga?
Hong Joo Ga had something to do with it. There's also something else that's strange.
The Hyeong, Hong Gi Joon, in your company is that family's youngest son.
Did you know that?
Eun Jo.
Business K: The person who lives again through Dae Seong Saccaromycetes.
Everything is done. It's all over now.
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
- Let's talk.
- No! I don't want to listen.
Eun Jo!
Where are you? Did you go to Dong Soo?
Dong Soo, you can't say anything to Hyo Seon.
I heard.
She left in such a state, and you just let her go alone?
Is there something wrong with Hyo Seon's taste buds? You should take her to the hospital.
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫
♫ Come to me.
Even if I live again ♫
♫ No matter how many times I am reborn ♫
♫ There isn't a day that I can live without you. ♫
♫ The love I will protect ♫
♫ The love I love because for me ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫